(Penny:)Oh. Well, then, good.
(Leonard:)I wasn't expecting such a crowd.
I'm nervous.
- It's okay. Open with a joke, you'll be fine.
- Okay, joke. Okay.
How about this? Um, okay.
(Leonard:)There's this farmer,
and he has these chickens...
(Leonard:)...but they won't lay any eggs.
(Leonard:)So he calls a physicist to help.
(Leonard:)The physicist then does some calculations
and he says:
"I have a solution, but it only works
for spherical chickens in a vacuum."
[ALL LAUGHING]
(Leonard:)Right?
Oh, sorry, I just... I've heard it before.
- Let's roll.
- Okay.
(Howard:)- Hey, nice suit.
- It's a classic, right?
I really should've brought my own car.
(Leonard:)So in conclusion, the data show that at
temperatures approaching absolute zero...
(Leonard:)...the moment of inertia changes
and the solid becomes a supersolid...